mxfastmoney.com 2016-04-22

# MX Fast Money Success System - MX Fast Money Privacy Policies

**> > MX Fast Money Privacy Policy << **

MX Fast Money is the only operator collecting or maintaining personal information through the www.mxfastmoney.com website.

We at MX Fast Money are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information or data that we collect about you lawfully and ethically.

By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit this website to make sure that you understand how any personal data you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this website only. If you link to other websites, please review the Privacy Policy posted at those websites.

COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

We at MX Fast Money collect personally identifiable data, like names and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The data you provide is used to fulfill your specific request for information about the MX Fast Money business. Aside from the information found in this website, we do send further information and updates via email, that's why we ask for your name and email address.

Unless you have given us your consent, we shall not send any type of email message to you except that which is related to your request, which is information about the MX Fast Money program.

TRACKING ACTIVITY

We at MX Fast Money may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our website. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this from happening.

DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION

We at MX Fast Money may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure on a secure server protected by password and firewall. Only authorized corporate staff of MX Fast Money have access to this information.

The names and email addresses collected are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties.

You have the choice to stop receiving further emails from MX Fast Money by clicking on the 'Unsubscribe' link at the lower part of any of our messages to you. Alternately you may send an email to MX Fast Money Admin with the word “UNSUBSCRIBE” at your discretion.

PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below:

MX FAST MONEY REGISTERED OFFICE

MillionaireX7 Global Incorporated  
Mill Mall Tower, 2nd Floor  
Wickhams Cay 1  
Road Town  
Tortola  
British Virgin Islands 1110  
Telephone: +63-939-253-3333  
Email: [admin@mxfastmoney.com](mailto:admin@mxfastmoney.com)

Note: This policy document along with all policy documents within our website must be reviewed and approved prior to use for your particular purpose. No statement of legality or compliance with any regulatory agencies is made in providing you with this document.
